

Contacts

+380974335970 rudomanovdmitrij@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/ https://github.com/

Tech Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SCSS
- GIT
- JavaScript
- WebPack
- React
- Deduv

Soft Skills

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Decision-making
- Leadership
- Creativity
- Stress management

Language Skills

- Russian : Native
- Ukrainian : Native
- English : Upper-intermediate

Front-End Developer

Dmitrij Rudomanov

I'm a Frontend developer with experience in building websites and APP`s. Whether you're trying to win work, list your services or even create a whole online store – I can help! I'm experienced in HTML and CSS3, SCSS, JS and React. Regular communication is really important to me, so let's keep in touch!

Project Experience

1.	PHONEBOOK Project Link
	Solo React-Redux project.Simple user friendly Pnonebook App
2.	FILMOTEKA Project Link [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript]
	JS team project with me as Teamlead. Movie site easy to use
3.	WEBSTUDIO Project Link HTML5, CSS3, SCSS]
	Educational markup project. Simple and Interactive
4.	ICECREAM Project Link
	Team project.lceCream selling web-site.Role:Developer,Code reviewer
5.	WOODER Project Link HTML5, CSS3, SCSS]
	Building an interesting landing website for wood furniture company
6.	OFDR Project Link [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript]
	Web-site for insurance companie.
7.	FUNIRO Project Link
	A modern web-store that sels best quality furniture
8.	LOGO Project Link
	Website for online Sport-shop
9.	BENTLEY Project Link
	Working on official Bentley web-page in Ukraine
ο.	LUX-TRADER Project Link
	Luxury Auctions Web-site with golden design.
1.	BINARY Project Link
	Modern innovative designers web-page.
2.	PRIME-ONE Project Link
	Web-Site for very creative foodmaking organiztion

...... [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS]

Simple but eyecatching landing page with vintage bikes.

Work Experience

13. BIKE | Project Link

Svet-LED Company

Web-site editor

September 2019 - January 2019 | Ukraine

- Editing the list of products on the site
- Products information update

Restaurant 'SHO PO CHEM'

Waiter

June 2019 - September 2019 | Ukraine

- Taking orders from visitors
- Customer service

Education

PSACEA

International Economics and business

September 2018 - June 2023 | Ukraine

Additional Education

GOIT

FULL STACK course online